<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The essential on</title><link>https://adno.app/en/docs/prologue/</link><description>Recent content in The essential on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 14:05:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adno.app/en/docs/prologue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Adno</title><link>https://adno.app/en/docs/prologue/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 19:08:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adno.app/en/docs/prologue/about/</guid><description>Adno is led by the Espace Mendès France a center for scientific, technical and industrial culture located in Poitiers and which operates throughout the Nouvelle-Aquitaine region (France). It is developing in partnership with Abbey of Saint-Savin-sur-Gartempe and the valley of frescoes, the Bibliothèque Sainte-Geneviève, Paris, the Cité internationale de la bande dessinée et de l&amp;rsquo;image, Angoulême, the Museums of Poitiers, the Natural History Museum of La Rochelle. Adno was selected as one of the sixteen winners of the 2022 edition of the call for innovative digital services projects by the french Ministry of Culture.</description></item><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://adno.app/en/docs/prologue/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 10:45:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adno.app/en/docs/prologue/quick-start/</guid><description>An online service #
The easiest way to get started is to use the online service. It is free and does not require registration. You can also start with an example.
Get started! Examples
As Adno is free software, you can also install it for yourself and others. The sources and installation instructions are available on Github.
👉 Adno is under development, its features and interface are subject to change.
Start a project #
The Adno home screen is divided into three areas.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://adno.app/en/docs/prologue/faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adno.app/en/docs/prologue/faq/</guid><description>Why Adno? #
Adno is a web application for visualizing, editing and sharing readings and pathways on images. It will be of particular interest to cultural and scientific mediators, as well as researchers, archivists, librarians, etc.
Read the About Adno page to learn more.
How do I use Adno? #
The easiest way is to join the online service. This documentation provides all the information you need to get started as well as a number of examples.</description></item></channel></rss>